(Sheldon:)You own a smoking monkey?
(Amy:)Don't be silly.
He's one of the animals
(Amy:)in my department's
nicotine addiction study.
(Sheldon:)What's he doing here?
(Amy:)I'm giving him emphysema.
(Amy:)The least I can do is let him
hang out and watch cable.
(Sheldon:)Remarkable.
(Sheldon:)Aren't you worried
about secondhand smoke?
(Penny:)A little.
The real danger is him biting
(Amy:)my face off while I'm sleeping.
(Sheldon:)Is he deliberately
blowing smoke at me?
(Amy:)Yeah. He's kind of an ass.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)May I share
something with you
(Sheldon:)that's troubling me?
(Amy:)Of course.
(Amy:)What's rattling around that
big bulbous head of yours?
(Sheldon:)Priya has essentially nullified
(Sheldon:)my roommate agreement
with Leonard,
(Sheldon:)making life in the apartment
very uncomfortable for me.
(Amy:)And you want me
to kill her? Done.